JESSICA TUCKER

2059 Allen Avenue, St. Louis, MO 63104 | H: 6185934273 | C: 6185934273 | jessicatucker09@yahoo.com

Summary

Energetic Event Coordinator with 7 years experience in personal and community events. I have coordinated events such as baby showers, large group discussions, photo shoots, dances, non profit events and more. I am willing to learn new skills and become an asset to Yoga Buzz.

Highlights

- Microsoft Office proficiency
- Excel spreadsheets
- Meticulous attention to detail
- Results-oriented
- Time management
- Professional and mature
- Fast Learner
- Dedicated team player
- Strong interpersonal skills
- Proofreading

Accomplishments

- 5 Baby Showers
- 2 photo shoots that were published in international magazines
- 10 large successful 50+ group events for the community
- Girl Empowerment meetings and activities
- Upcoming international fashion I am head producer/coordinator
- 10 years of learning to decorate and coordinate

Experience

Account Executive

American Express — St. Louis, MO

Mar 2016 to Current

The Accounts Receivable and Collections Executive is responsible for developing and maintaining accounting principles, practices and procedures to ensure accurate and timely financial statements. The Accounts Receivable and Collections Executive ensures that work is properly completed in a timely and accurate manner. This position addresses tight deadlines and a multitude of accounting activities including general ledger preparation, financial reporting, yearend audit preparation and the support of budget and forecast activities. The Accounts Receivable and Collections Executive will have contact with the organizations executive leaders and Controller which requires strong interpersonal communication skills both written and verbal.

Corrections Officer

Feb 2015 to Feb 2016

City of St. Louis — St. Louis, MO

Monitored and investigated suspicions persons and situations and unusual activities. Organized and recorded facts to prepare incident reports Supervise inmates in housing units and those segregated for administrative or punitive measures; instruct inmates in housekeeping and sanitation; supervise the issuance of clothing and other personal effects to inmates. Observe signs of tension and distress in residents. Prepared report for Lieutenants and Captains to review. Used the IJMS computer software.

Administrative Assistant New Age Truth — St. Louis, MO Apr 2007 to Jan 2013

Planned travel arrangements for 12 executives and staff. Drafted meeting agendas, supplied advance materials and executed follow-up for meetings and team conferences. Managed the receptionist area, including greeting visitors and responding to telephone and in-person requests for information. Handled all media and public relations inquiries. Planned meetings and prepared conference rooms.

Education

High School Diploma, General Studies Cahokia High School — Edwardsville, IL, United States Top 10% of Class Recipient of New Age Truth and Sigma Gamma Rho Scholarships

3 years Finished, Nursing SIUE — Edwardsville, IL On Deans List for 3 semesters

Certified Java Developer, Java Development LaunchCode Mentor Center — St. Louis, MO, United States Certificate in Computer Operations Certificate in Development and Management 2009

2018